When you leave here where are you going, Madam?
Yola.
To whom?
I stay with my mum.
Because I’m seeing you living on your own.
What is wrong with you?
You are frustrated.
Yes, sir.
And this frustration has led you to do many things which you don’t want to do.
And you are tired now.
Yes, sir.
There was a man you were with for some time and you left.
- Yes, sir.
- What happened?
There was something you discovered.
This is your daughter.
Yes, sir.
I say that your daughter is a troubled daughter.
I have problems.
We came all the way from Yola.
We came from Yola.
You don’t know what is happening.
Yes, sir, I don’t know even in my own life.
Let's go.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Doris.
I am from Yola.
Last week Sunday, the Man of God walked up to me and prophesied.
He asked me where I was going from here.
He saw me living alone and that I was frustrated and tired.
That has caused me to do things that I did not want to do.
He said that I broke up with a man because I discovered something
and that I was a troubled daughter which was very true and correct.
When he asked me where I was going from here, I said Yola but in Yola things were so difficult for us.
Our rent has expired and we have no money to pay for the house rent.
People look at me as if I was OK and as if I have money but I had nothing.
This caused frustration.
I even tried to stab myself many times to kill myself but my mum would come and hold me.
I was just tired of the life I was living.
I have no work, nothing.
Look at me; I ought to be married but no man is coming.
So, what the man of God said concerning you was correct while asking where were you going -
you actually have nowhere to go now.
Yes.
OK. Can we hear a word or two from your mother?
I believe she also has something to say
Emmanuel!
(God with us – Matthew 1:23)
We are from Yola.
When we came here, the man of God prophesied to my daughter that she was a troubled daughter.
Then, I got up and said yes and even myself.
Later, the man of God said that we should come and see him.
So, our lives are miserable.
Even when he asked where we were going to…
We have nowhere to go.
We have no destination.
We have nowhere to go because right now, we have nothing.
She wants to kill herself; she wants to stab herself.
Anytime she takes a knife to kill herself, I would hold her.
I would talk to her saying that she should believe in God because
God is the God that makes impossible possible.
Before we came here, I was thinking how it would be possible for us to come because there was no way.
Somebody gave me some things to sell.
I then took her and said, come, let's run to our father, T.B. Joshua.
I think this is the last bus stop.
So, madam, we just want to hear from you.
You can see the old woman shedding tears because of the situation they have been in, for years.
You said the man of God had prophesied that your daughter was a troubled child.
Can you tell us more about these troubles that your child was facing, before the prophecy was given,
during the last service?
The trouble she is facing is that she has no job, no husband or helper.
Even to eat is difficult and she has no house.
So, she decided that she was going to kill herself.
Several times, I’ve collected the knife from her.
Even rat poison – she would say she would drink it and I’d collect it from her.
The troubles of your child - how they affected you, as a mother?
It has affected me.
Even right now, I am having heart problems.
The mother and the lady - when you listen to them...
You cannot blame them for their misfortune.
When we work, God still has to examine it.
That is; after you have done everything, humanly, God would still have to go through it and mark it.
Can you see?
After you have done it perfectly to you, you cannot say, "It's alright".
God still will go through it and mark it one by one.
That is what you call grace.
After you have moved or walked you say, "Yes, I do it perfectly" - as a Christian, that language is not right.
Yes.
As Christians we live under the grace - the grace covers us.
After you have moved or walked, done everything you could humanly,
and you say this was a right thing you have done - leave it for God.
God will still have to what?
Mark it.
So, it is up to God to give you a mark, whether it is 90%, 50%, 40% or ... it is over to God.
This is grace.
If anyone now say that this family is to be blamed, or you ask them, "You have hands and legs -
why can't you go and work?"
You need to ask yourself by what authority you achieved what you achieved.
The women - they have nowhere to live.
Mere look at their appearance and attire - very expensive and good looking -
but that could not confuse the Spirit of God.
The attire and everything were of the past glory.
Past what?
(Glory.)
Past glory - those things they had in the past.
So, the mother and the daughter...
We have learned that the house rent is not less that N200,000.
They should give them N500,000 to start something.
PITIFUL: Elderly Mother Finds Daughter Drinking Rat Poison!!!
The man of God said the sum of N500,000 should be given to them to support the woman and her daughter.
You can see the woman's tears of joy that leak on her cheek.